A Guide to the Karl Landsteiner papers, Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research Scientific Staff FA126
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject File / Lab Notes, 1911-1984; 1925-1943; 3; 11.2 Cubic Feet
  - "Ovalbumin Digest Products (Peptic Digestion) " [Chase Expts], 1934 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Ovalbumin Experiments", circa 1938 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - "Ovalbumin Experiments", 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - [Ovalbumin] "Inhibition tests with Ovalbumin I.S.", 1939 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - "Ovalbumins, Procedures on Preparations of", circa 1939-1941 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - '"Ox Splits' as agglutinins", circa 1931-1932 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - "P-amino... Anilic Acids,-P-nitro...", circa 1932 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - "P and D Analyses", circa 1928-1929 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - [P], "Experiments with P. 13b old protocol w/P"], 1929-1930 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "Paper #180" [German and Dutch texts], undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - "Dr Parker, Experiments for", circa 1935-1938 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    [Also includes tests for Dr Carrel.
  - "Parker Experiments", 1936-1937 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - "Parker, Exp. Old", 1936-1937 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - "Parker Work", 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "Pauling", circa 1940-1942 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - "Pauling dye experiment" [MWC note 1984], 1942 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - "Pauling [notes and drawings re proteins], circa 1937 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - "Pauling 2 work", circa 1935-1938 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    [Includes KL notes on readings, references].
  - "Pepsin", 1935 November 11 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - "Pepsin II", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - "Pepsin; A substance from", 1935 October-circa 1936 March (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - "Pepsin A", undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - "Pepsin, beef A substance", 1936 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - "Pepsin, pig A [Substance] ", circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Pepsin, Pig (Fairchild) A substance Also beef pepsin Mucin F", 1936 1941 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - "Pepsin, purification of, for digestion" [Chase], circa 1933-1935 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - [Peptides], circa 1939 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - "Peptides-Concluded Series...", circa 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "Peptides, Long chain", circa 1936-1938 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - "Peptides, nitro and amino-benzoyl", circa 1933 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - [Peptides, proteins notes], undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - "Peptide syntheses-2 methods", circa 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "Peptides, Synthetic", circa 1930 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - [Synthetic Peptides] "Specificity", circa 1934-1937 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - "Peuta peptide-immune sera", 1936-1938 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - "Phasin", 1934-1935 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "Phasin", circa 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "Phasin I Letters", 1936 1938 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - "Phasin II notes", circa 1934 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Phasin III References", undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - "Phasin IV Reprints I", 1932-1933 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - "Phasin V Reprints II", 1927 1932-1933 1935 1938 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - "Phasin VI Reprints III", 1933-1936 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - "Phasin; Nigg Protocols", 1933-1936 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - "Phenoliptalein Expts", circa 1940 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - [Photocopied, Landsteiner Material [by Chase]], undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - "Picryl Atoxyl immune sera", 1937 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - "Dr Pirie's Experiments", circa 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - "Pn XIV Expts Goebel", 1938 1940 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - "Pn Work", 1939 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - "Poison Ivy Geranyl catechol. Chase, Harte, Jacobs", 1930 1935 1939 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - "Post Jacobs Expts/KL", circa 1937 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - "Precipitin, Chimp, Human", circa 1932 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - "Precipitin, Qualitative Relations", 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - "Precipitin tests with dyes", circa 1932-1939 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - "Preparions"[Preparation of phenyl butyric acid, phenyl caproic acid. Pheny isocrotanic acid; nitro & NH-Mandelic & others], circa 1931-1932 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - "Preparations", 1932, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - "Preparations-Landsteiner-Black", circa 1936-1942 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - "Preparations, Miscellaneous 1932-33", circa 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Protoamine", circa 1936 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "Protoambulose, Fractionation of", circa 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - "Proto and Deutero Sheep. June 1933 tests Portion published", 1933 June (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - "Proto, pig", 1933 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "Pseudo [?]; Reiner Sera; Pneumonia Sera...", 1931 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - "Pyramidon Expts", circa 1936 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - "Quinine Expts", circa 1941 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "Quotations" [notebook], undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - "Rabbits Breeding", undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - "Rats and guinea pigs", 1931 September (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - [Landsteiner references], undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - [References], undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - [reprints and reference re Levine, Wiener, Kozeika], circa 1929 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - "Rh Early Correspondence", 1941 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - "Rh experiments American Indians", circa 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Rh factor Ms, circa 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - "Rhesus blood, final tests with, I. S. from G. pigs & rabbits", undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - "Rhesus & Human precipitin tests", 1942 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - "Rhesus Immune sera", circa 1939-1941 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - "Rh, Families for", 1943 March 10-May 10 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - "Rh tests and protocoled, Families completed for", circa 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Ricine & Beans & Lentils, circa 1931-1932 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "Ricine. G. Pig blood I. s. also with Carbo Raffin", 1942 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - "Rockland State Hospital, bloods from 1933-Pearl River 8-21" [Chase note 1984], circa 1932-1934 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - "Rockland State Hospital" [requests for blood specimens], circa 1932-1934 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - "Rot splitter of A substance', circa 1934-1936 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - "Rot 8A and 3283 data, 1935-1936", circa 1935-1939 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - "Rothen", circa 1932 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - [Rothen Exp] "6/24/40 ov. i. s. given to Dr Rothen...", circa 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - "Rothen", circa 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    [Includes material on Linus Pauling].
  - "Rothen [?] Phasin", circa 1939 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - "Routine readings Book 24", 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - "Saliva", circa 1931-1936 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - "Saliva Digestion" [Chase note 1984], 1935 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - "Saliva, Horse I" [note by Chase 1984], circa 1930-1932 1934 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - "Saliva, Horse II", circa 1932-1933 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Saliva, Horse III", 1933-1934 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Saliva, Horse IV", 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Saliva, Horse", 1935 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Saliva, Horse", circa 1934-1938 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "Saliva, Horse" [notes, references, reprints], circa 1931-1937 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "Saliva substance I, II, III" 9/1932-6/1933, 4/1934-6/1934, 11/1934-6/1935 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Saliva substance IV-V" 9/35-10/35, 11/36 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "Saliva" [with letters from Erik Jorpes], circa 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - "Salts, solubilities", 1940 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - "Salvarsan", 1936-1938 1940-1941 1943 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - "Salvarsan samples", undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - "Salvarsan tests [Book 20], 1935-1936 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - "Saponin..." [note by Chase], 1931 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - "Schiff, Vita, publications, etc. Rheinbolt", circa 1933-1935 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - "Schumacher" [correspondence & reprints, re translation of article by Dr Willy Schumacher on use of blood tests, and eventual publication in St. John's College Law Review. ], circa 1932-1934 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - [Scrapbook (contains notes of English phrases) ], circa 1922 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "Sensitizations 1932-33 2: 4 Dinitrochlorobenzene Neosalvarsan I Nitroso dimethylaniline 1933-1934 Book 5", 1932-1934 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - "Sensitizations 1932-1933 suberaniticacid epds Specificity tests + II Miscellaneous substances Special tests 1933-1934. Book 6", 1932-1934 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "Sensitizations, 1935-1936 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - [Sensitizations with simple substances], 1934-1935 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - [Sera] tests, circa 1931 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - "Serological tests on aliphatic side chain substances 1932", 1931-1932 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "Serum tests", circa 1933 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - "Shiga" [and paratyhoid], 1931-1932 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - "Silk" [Chase Exps], 1933-1934 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "Silk", 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - "Silk Exp[t] ", 1940-1941 1943 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - "Silk Expts. 1941 Summary Protocols", circa 1933 1941-1943 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - "Silk Folder I", 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - "Silk Folder II 1938", circa 1937-1939 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - "Silk Fractions, Electrometric titrations", circa 1941 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - [Silk Hydrolysis products], undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - "Silk, old notes" [notes and letters with references, reprints], circa 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - [Silk] "Preparation of silk antigen [for immunization]", circa 1943 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - [Silk preparation lab tests], circa 1939-1941 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - "Silk protocols for year of September 1942 (Hoovar, Meier)" (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - "Silk protocols (final) January to July 1943 (H. Tetenbaum)" (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - "Skin Sensitization", 1936-1937; [Book 1 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - "Skin Sensitization", 1936-1937; [Book 2 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - "Skin test, Miscellaneous" [Book 8], circa 1934 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - "Specificity test & miscellaneous (positive expts) & ivy like compounds" [book 21], 1935-1936 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "Straight chains chemistry", circa 1930-1931 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - "Storma", circa 1934-1938 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "Sulfonic acids", circa 1934-1938 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - [Sulfonic acids notes, ud], undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - "Sulfoxy-Salvarsan", circa 1936-1937 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "Tables: Johannsen, Schiff paper; Wellisch paper; [illegible names] Bernstein Wellisch correction", undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - [Tests of various substances] Abrin-Horse serum, 1936-1940 1942 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - [Tests of various substances] Iodoform-Ragweed, 1937-1938 1941 1943-1944 1946 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - [Test of various substances], circa 1935-1936 1939-1940 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - "Thiere", 1922-1923 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - "Thiere", 1923-1924 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - "T[h]yroxin... Ascaris", circa 1936 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - "Tiber-Bellin", 1931 January-June (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - "Tissue culture data", [circa 1912, 1929, 1934, 1936] (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - "Todd" [Chase note 1984], 1935 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - "Todd Expts 19A Isoimmunization Chickens", circa 1930-1931 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - "Toxins (Ricin, Castor Bean) [Reprint], 1904-1905 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - [Transfusion, Blood Transfusion Betterment Association Meetings], 1930-1931 1935 1937 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - [Transfusion, Blood Transfusion Betterment Association Meetings], 1940 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - [Transfusion, Blood Transfusion Betterment Association Meetings], 1941 January-1942 October (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - [Transfusion, Blood Transfusion Betterment Association Reports and duplicated memoranda, notes, etc], circa 1929-1942 undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - [Transfusion, Forms, Record books, Printed information], circa 1932 1936 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - "Transfusion, Jones Paper", 1928 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - "Transfusion (letters) etc", circa 1930 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - [Transfusion Miscellaneous: Notes, References, ms, clipping, transcript], undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - [Transfusion Reprints], 1936 1941 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - "Trypanosomas", 1925-1926 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - "Ursol", circa 1934 1937 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - [Ursol (other unidentified notes), circa 1937-1938 1940 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - "Ursohiol", circa 1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - "Van der Scheer and Hunter Factors", circa 1933 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    [Includes MWC Correspondence].
  - "Van der Scheer and Hunter, Main Experiments", circa 1930-1936 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - "Van der Scheer Lechithin Abstracts", 1925-1926 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - "Van der Scheer-Notebook-Horse RBC Antigens", circa 1924 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - [Van der Scheer notes], circa 1932 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - "Van der Scheer Preliminary experiments on Immunizations with organs", 1924-1925 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - "Wards Island Duplicate List", circa 1928 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - "Wards Island List of Patients", circa 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - "Wards Island Old Correspondence", circa 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - "Wards Island recent correspondence", circa 1932-1934 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - [Weiner, Dr A. S. data on Families from], circa 1943 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - "Dr Weinstein III...", circa 1931 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - "Words" [Lists of English words and phrases], circa 1943 undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - "Work, new" [notes, references, reprints], circa 1936-1941 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - "Work, new-problems", circa 1933-1940 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - "Work, Var." [notes, references, reprints], circa 1932-1943 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - "Zein...", 1939 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Manuscripts, 1931-1940; 4; 0.67 Cubic Feet
  Includes Edinburgh ms ("On Some (Recent) Aspects of Individual Blood Reactions"), "Molecular Structure and Intermolecular Forces" ms, Rh factor ms, "Specificity of Serological Reactions" ms, and "Systemic Anaphylaxis, Organ Anaphylaxis".
  - "Edinburgh", undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - "Edinburgh", undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    [Includes drafts of ms "On some recent aspects of individual blood reaction"].
  - "Edinburgh" [notes, reprints, & mss; especially re work of P. Levine & A. S. Weiner, circa 1940 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - [Landsteiner ms in German], undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - [Landsteiner mss], undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - [Landsteiner mss], undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - "Molecular structure and intermolecular forces" [Ms], undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - [Remarks concerning Landsteiner's discovery of isoaggluniation and blood groups with special reference to a paper by J. A. Kennedy] Zinser, H & Cora, A. F.], 1931 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - [Rh factor Ms], circa 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - [Specificity of Serological reactions (SSR)] "Book", undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - [Specificity of Serological Reactions (SSR)] "Galley", undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - [SSR manuscripts-revisions], undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - [SSR] "2nd revised page proofs...", circa 1936 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - "Specificity of Serological Reactions Ch II 1 of 2", undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - "Specificity of Serological Reactions Ch II 2 of 2", undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Specificity of Serological Reactions Ch III 1 of 2", undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - "Specificity of Serological Reactions Ch III 2 of 2", undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - "Specificity of Serological Reactions Ch V 1 of 2", undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - "Specificity of Serological Reactions Ch V 2 of 2", undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - [SSR] "Charles C. Thomas Publisher" [Correspondence], 1933-1936 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - [Systemic anaphylaxis, organ anaphylaxis], undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Landsteiner Reprints, 1892-1943; 5; 1 Cubic Feet
  - [Reprints 1-32, 34-36], 1892-1904 1944 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - [Reprints 37-40, 42-53, 55-67, 69-75], 1904-1907 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - [Reprints 76-85, 87-88, 90-103, 106], 1907-1909 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - [Reprints 107-115,117-122, 124-128, 130-135], 1909-1913 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - [Reprints 136-148,150,152-156], 1913-1916 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - [Reprints 157-187], 1916-1923 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - [Reprints 188-206], 1923-1925 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - [Reprints 207-228], 1925-1927 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - [Reprints 229-253], 1927-1929 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - [Reprints 254-281], 1929-1931 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - [Reprints 283-288, 290-307], 1932-1936 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - [Reprints 308-336, 338-343], 1936-1943 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Reprints Assorted, 1913 1917 1919 1921-1924 1932-1933 1935 1937 1939 1942 1947 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Reprints by other Scientists, 1902-1940; 6; 0.8 Cubic Feet
  - Bailey, G. Howard (Heterophile Studies), 1928 1931 1933 1934 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Boivin, Mesrobeanu, Combiesco, 1933-1935; 1 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Boivin, Mesrobeanu, Combiesco, 1936-1938; 2 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Brown, Wade H., 1915 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Burnet, F. M., 1934 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Carrel, Alexis R., 1912 1926 1927 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Creech, H. j., 1937-1939 1941 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Dean, H, R, and R. A. Webb, 1926 1928 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Doerr, R., 1913-1914 1921-1922 1925-1926 1933 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Erlenmeyer, Hans and Erwin Berger, 1931-1937 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Fierz, H. E., 1937-1939 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Harrington, C. R., 1937-1939 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Haurowitz, Felix, 1932 1933 1936 1940 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Hirst, George K., 1941 1942 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Hooker, Sanford B. and William C. Boyd, 1931-1934 1939 1940 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Horsefall, Frank L., 1935-1937 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Huntoon, F. M., 1920 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Ivanovics, G., 1937-1940 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Lancefield, Rebecca C., 1925 1928 1933 1934 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Marrack, John, 1931 1932 1938 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Morgan, W. T. J., 1931-1933 1935-1937 1940 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Pine, N. W., 1939 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Snapper, I, 1935 1936 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Special Allergy, 1902 1904 1906 1934 1936 1938 1939 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Witebsky, E., 1927-1930 1932 1933 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Wormall, Arthur, 1933 1934 1936 1938 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Posthumous Files, 1946-1984 1961-1980; bulk; 7; 0.6 Cubic Feet
  Includes correspondence and notes of Merrill Chase, Landsteiner first day cover and stamp, and 1968 NY Academy of Science Conference.
  - Chase: American Association of Blood banks, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Chase: Annals of the NY Academy of Sciences Vol. 169, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Chase: Blood Bank Association of NY State, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Chase: Blood Group Nomenclature Papers, 1965-1968 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Chase: Conference NY Academy of Science, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Chase: Dinner NY Academy of Science, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Chase: New York University Hall of Fame Nomination, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Chase: Funding for the NY Academy of Science Conference, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Chase: Landsteiner First Day Cover and Stamp, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Chase: Ortho Research Course on Immunology, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Chase: Publication in Academy Annals (Boyd Manuscript), 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Chase: Typescript of notes, 1982 1984 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Dover Publications [Correspondence re reprint of "The Specificity of Serological Reactions"], 1961-1963 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - "Hunter, Charles RBC" [MW Chase file], 1951-1952 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory Methods 1973 [Explanations by MW Chase with note], 1984 January 11 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - [Miscellaneous notes], 1970 1980 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - "Phage-proteus 6", 1944 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Pharmacopia-Folder 1-old & copies, 1946-1948 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Photocopied Material-Weiner/Levine Controversy, 1942-1943 1969 1973 1975 1980 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Photocopies, undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - [Saliva, Horse: From (25) 16 "Saliva, Horse I"], circa 1980 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Lantern Slides, 8
  - Lantern Slides (Box 40)